Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show Star shine is so
Tell me how you think I'm wrong, when I say I feel so lost
Tell me why you think you're love, erase all that it cost
Tell me why you look at me, like I'm just a piece of dust
Tell me how you
When I give away my trust
pretty clean today. It took a while, decent, huh? But yeah, unfortunately, you get a little
dirty and I have to clean them. You can always clean them. Like, I've been a lot worse than
How are we doing today?
What does this person say?
Now you just need to learn to wash your grease ball hair
and shave the neck beard.
Oh my gosh, is that the real vegan Patriot?
I don't think that's the real vegan Patriot.
And my hair is washed.
I just got out of the bath or shower.
So I don't know what you mean by that.
And neck beard, well, whatever, I like to...
Let it grow like it wants to grow, but I'll shave when I want to shave
Go fuck yourself
There's not the real vegan Patriot, I think we just verified it now. I'm a mod. Just told me
Sock count hey
Hmm
It does feel nice to be
Ooh, there's some freebies of Epic Games guys. Do you play video games? There's a store called Epic Games
You can get like free
Games there
I'll see if there's anything good
I'm on a three months. I think on my VR headset. They get three months free. They offer me just three months for free
So that's pretty cool
Of this like you can use a bunch of games, right?
What am I looking at epic? Okay, EP I see
So this company gives but there's this company epic it gives way like three video games a month
sign in and get them
Because I always forget you have to claim them within a certain amount of time, you know
Man, ooh, I think I remembered it or it's not right. Hi, babe
Continue. Yes, right now
Maybe later
Hey, babe, okay, let's see store
Okay
Okay, so they have firestone idle online idle freedom
Looks okay
I like free things part of my astrological side. I like free things and I like
okay
Like discounts and I like are they good deals now
Place like team who cannot give my interest
Because I mean they can but it's like they can't like it's hard. I need to like just have something I want to buy
They're really cheap
I'm not gonna shop on team who right?
I mean, I I mean for most things I will I mean
Okay, what can I say? It's like so much better prices, but there's some things like you know, I probably want to
You know, you want to buy always buy things made in the USA and things like that. That's cool
Like look for that kind of stuff, but
Almost everything we buy is from China, but that's you know, I've been wrong with it
Just probably we're paying it. We were overpaying for a lot of stuff, you know
And I like to
Think cool stuff a good deal just like that and I do usually find cool stuff at a good deal like
Glasses, hey, I was on the show last night. I was on Sam and not say yeah on Sam and yeah
It was like not horrible to me
Um, basically I was responding to blogger and stuff like that and I haven't really like short-term memory about like
When I'm at like what we fight about or anything we fight it at all or anything so I don't really like stay mad at ever
About things and I say and I'm glad people some other people some people do do things to take things a little bit
Pretty personally some people have a good
You know are cool about things and I'd like people that are cool about things
I want to try to be cooler than I am about things, but it's just like
What cool? What is cool cool is like not really caring sometimes, right? Oh, there's the $30 game. That's pretty cool
Okay, so
I'm not gonna like worry about negative stuff said anymore. It's like
I'm gonna focus more than positive
I'm gonna try right we all should try this
Oh, you know sometimes we will have to be faced with a lot of negative, right?
Okay, well the things that there are three free bees. I don't see the two so there's usually two so it's probably lying
So I'll get back to the page
How are we doing let's see so no one's talking or anything
Should we see back hopefully maybe if I play a video that you like it. I don't know you like my videos
Steal from the mountain sun
Voice of the dawn where the climb's begun
Words like pillars fire in my hands
I build a temple on shifting sand
Capricorn rising, storm in my eyes
Aquarius moonlight, thunder, cracks of sky
Secrets I keep, visions awake with a dream of sleep
Screams of justice, trial and bow, visions made flesh I declare
Captain's porch at the edge of sea, a scar
Ah, that's one of the cool things I've been playing.
Yeah, and actually that stuff is based on my astrology.
And like I'm a Capricorn rising, also Capricorn sun
and an Aquarius moon all in the first house.
And if anyone wants me to go through their astrology
with them, whether they wanna like just do like a quick
a quick going over of like what it you know, basically a basic chart thing or they want to go in depth about something particular
There's a lot of really cool stuff you can find out through astrology and it's like I find I keep finding more and more things that they really
Prove it to me that it works then that there's something to it more than oh shit. Oh shit. What's going on here? Oh
My god
There's candle wax. I've gotten spilled and my card was out of the shit. I
Don't know how the candle wax got spilled that no reveal
Ooh, it's a wax got all over this
Three of wands
What could that mean?
Could mean that which is closer to that anybody what does it say? It's a oh, this is the one about
You know making progress, but be on on unsure waters, right? I really do that
Hi everybody go ahead and say hi to me
Everyone's usually so quiet here. Is everyone like able to talk in the chat?
I mean I'm not being sarcastic
I mean like is there like are you guys like blocked just come on another account and tell me
Look into it, but as long as you're like a nice person, right?
So who is this on this boat?
Wonder
Some other guy looking for Moby Dick, what is it? Stacey of doubt?
Now maybe my McDonald's oh, yeah McDonald's give me some
Yeah, I meant I friend to prank him over the other day, and I
Did for them, okay
Hi Brad good morning, how are you?
Okay, well, thank you. I thought it's built like milk over the carburetor's candle back that's got a splash
I'll go over the table. Oh
This is good this new
Lucky there nicely
Wax covered anyway, so you just wipe it off
Yeah, good morning everybody
We're having a great one
Yeah, but you know I was on Samans for a little bit less than I didn't get kicked off for the first time in like a while
right, but I mean not by him because he usually like you know doesn't kick me off, but by
People like clapping me and so
But it didn't happen last night. I was just on for a few minutes. They want me to comment on blogger
Did you and see you're good? I'm hope I'm very well
I'm very well
Okay, cut that off. Of course
rent spanking new
You wouldn't even know okay
So
McDonald's it's like, yeah, I mean that hash brown was a good image. It's like it's good
But you get it. It just went too fast. I'll still have it was funny
Which did you watch?
Maybe I missed a comment home you cleans going at each other
Who is that? Oh, bro. Oh, the only sort of blogger thing. Oh
It wasn't like
bad, but I
Was pretty I pretty much got him
Hey Nancy, it was funny. I just went on for a few minutes. It's funny. You're the end of Sam & Joe beat it was on the panel and
you know, I guess Barry got docs or something like that and
His pictures and you know, Eldos using his picture because you know, Eldo loves to
and do that, right?
And then, yeah, then I called in
and he was like, oh, you know,
I just don't like Psych because, you know,
he's, I think the two reasons he gave is like, you know,
he has like weirdos on his show.
And then, you know, and then he,
and then the other thing was like,
he was like, oh, he's so too focused on money
and stuff like that.
And they already brought up earlier
Like to blog or they're like, oh, you know blogger, you know, you're like, you know, your cashups always on the screen or something like that
It's always incorporated like really strong. And he's like, yeah, no, there's no way what I'm trying to make money, you know
So it's like, but I'm not ashamed of it
Of monetizing the channel in any way I can it's like, you know
But you know you guys really helped me along too, and so I appreciate it
Especially you know people that do memberships and stuff like that appreciate a few good memberships like Brad's a member. That's awesome
And I'm a member I even like buy myself a membership just so I can have like the I don't know if it makes my name green or blue, but I
Can find out when I type in my
Yeah, but you know it didn't but yeah, but anyway my response to blogger was
To why I weirded on my show is that well, he does too because he has this guy named blackout Andy
Like sitting as his co-host basically on a show and blackout Andy so like really really strange really strange
I was gonna say no, it's like yeah, he does have kind of like a
Those speech I'm not gonna make fun people with speech impediments not for that reason
But he's just also a jerk to me
He's like obsessed with wanting to pour on me like every time he comes to the show and then he's like
He like hid me in his last chat for like no reason at all like nothing
I did nothing. I was just like, you know pleasant in the chat and like and he was just that he just doesn't like me
And he thinks that I don't know if he doesn't like gay people or whatever
But but anyway bloggers like didn't have anything to say about that and they even made a worse allegation about black
Annie that I'm not gonna repeat because it's kind of gross and I mean really gross, but it's like kind of probably inappropriate to
To say but and I wouldn't want to accuse people of that, but I didn't know I didn't hear him saying himself
Yeah, but he can be a jerk to me. He's been a totaler. Hey, how are you doing Nancy Nancy and Brad? Yeah
And I do wish people well and I believe anybody can improve themselves and like also have
regrets for like their past and things like that.
Like I like every saint has a past, every sinner has a future.
And so once I work, I think God, he said, did you have a fortune cookie and say, no,
I think it's a famous quote from someone I don't know who said it, but I do love that
quote because it's just like so true.
If you look at the lives of the saints like the Catholic saints and things like that they they sometimes some of them had very sinful lives and things like that, right and
And then they like had like revelations or they had like the experiences or
I don't wonder like what's required for sainthood these days
Five pounds old episode on
This is old
But it's good, it's worth sort of seeing I did I never saw this
Or is it
I don't remember doing it really either. I mean I do remember saying it but I think I was talking about tarot at the time
Or on tarot
um
There's a devil card, right
and
I
Big pharma and shoe companies are furious that this doctor
No, no, no. So you go loud LD 15 back on your panel. You know it about the law, right? How many times people got to tell you site
So wait on those receipts salmon. No, I'm not. There's no need for receipts. You're weird. Oh niggas
Bro go back with just Jen bro go back with your sister the fucking dog and you're weird
Oh, you talked to miners on on on on YouTube. We all know this you admitted
But know who the
You've been on jimmy panel. You even ban on jimmy panel site how many times you got it how many times people got to tell you about this ld 15, dude
well
I don't know. I really don't want to watch that one. Hold on. I want to watch a different one.
This is about, and this is the one, and before I met Alex, she was battling pebs or something. Let me see.
Pretty interesting.
Ice with bonuses up to $50,000 and generous benefits. Join.ice.gov.
Join Ice.
Someone who doesn't treat ear ringing is gambling their health.
I know this might sound a little crazy, but if you've got that...
Hello?
Yeah. Is Pep still on here?
Yep.
Okay, I got a question for you pet.
Bicycle bitch, bicycle bitch.
Why are you leaving?
I'm not leaving, I'm just not talking to you.
You are insane.
Well, you can answer when I leave the channel.
I don't need to answer anything.
You need to answer for a lot when it comes to what you've been up to, little girl.
I don't have to answer you.
You're not my master, bitch.
I actually am.
You're not my master, bitch, unless it works for me.
You're not my master, bitch.
First it was controlling, now it's me.
Why do you got your aides around?
A few months ago.
Oh, that's legally actionable slander. Legally actionable slander. Shit you do every day.
Yeah, why are you trying to destroy your boyfriend's business? Because that's all you've been doing.
That's why they knocked that guy Ron's other alt off. That's what we're trying to figure out.
You seem like you love this man. You have some issues. I'm asking you, you don't want to answer
Oh, Alex, Alex, weren't you cool with peps? Right? Now you fall out with her. Come on,
man. You got to, you got to, you got to stop flip flopping. Okay. Come on, get it together,
man. You hear me? Is peps going to answer any questions? Absolutely not you disgusting. You
spoke on her kid and she's disgusting. Pebs, stop talking if you don't want to answer any. Listen,
listen, you spoke on her kids. We don't appreciate it. You spoke on her kids. You're disgusted.
No, the audience is speaking on her children for two dollars the entire fuck-up you disgusting piece of shit
Pebs you don't have any content if it's not for me and the same thing happened with control
about shit, because you're begging people, begging people to cover your content.
I'm in Australia, I'm everywhere, and then I come to the International Drive.
You get three viewers. The most viewers you've got were covering me and Zaya.
You get three fucking viewers that scared you to the bitch.
You can't stand alone, that's sad. Dirty pussy bitch. I hope Donny has fucked you up.
Whoa, no, nothing's gonna happen to me, but here's the question happen to you. Okay. Why don't you go take a vacation in Yuma?
Okay, why don't you?
Put an international drive and cam up go to Yuma. Go to Yuma. Why did you even leave HS3?
That's none of your fucking business dumb bitch. You make it everybody's business.
It's none of your fucking business. Why I left. Why don't you get your
You make it everybody's business. Yuma Arizona. You don't understand how this works.
The Lutz to Amber having a warrant out on this dirty bitch on panel.
How many times are you going to throw your boyfriend under the bus because
He tried to help you and now you're trying to thwart.
What happened to that fucking stupid Zaya and top said all of that on panel the day before you fucking retard.
Pebs you said you were going to answer any questions yet you're answering the questions.
That's how fucking I'm scared fake please call I'm faking calling the police. Oh my God I'm scared.
I'm going to assault Zaya on a live stream.
At this point, you have gone to police through your own
I'm a cop calling Karen. You're damn right I am.
You are a cop calling Karen.
I am a cop calling Karen.
The next word is going to be for you, bitch.
You're going to have two warrants soon.
You absolutely are.
You're going to have two warrants soon, bitch.
Soon you won't be able to come to Orlando.
Just like you can't go to Yuma, you dirty bitch.
I don't think anyone wants to go to Yuma, peps.
I know you don't want to go to Yuma because you'll be lost.
Why would anyone go to Yuma?
Why? Why would anyone go there?
I know why you won't go,
because you're going to be in a fucking cage where you belong.
Oh, in a cage?
Uh-uh.
In a cage.
Yeah, that's what they had in these cages.
Okay, let me guess my white supremacist now because I said that we're all everybody up here
So we know that you have issues with black women. We know I don't have any issues
Oh, yes, you do. You're disgusting. You've had issues with so many black women for content
You're so fucking hard. The only reason that you have anything to talk about
Alex you realize you get three viewers the most viewers you got were when you fucking pretended you were scared and called the the fake police
The most viewers you've ever fucking got until you were fucking
It's for money entertain the cop calling karen's because of you
Cool. Well, you're about to be arrested soon from there. Are you are you going to pay him for his phone? You owe him 500 by the way
So here's me what?
On live and the case has already been closed
It hasn't been those bits.
That's not how it works.
You forgot I'm a cop.
I already know how it works.
You're just a constant liar.
That's all you are.
And you think people believe you.
Cubs, you were just called out for your lies on your own screen.
Oh my god.
And wham, wham, wham.
No, are you ever here's the main question? This is what everyone wants to know. Are you ever going to say I'm using a clap coin
Cut this ugly dirty a to the festive bitch
Alex you're using a token. I'm sorry
Get the fuck out of here you dirty disgusting. Have a good night. Have a good night
It's okay
See that was it was a good until it's one, you know, then she can like kick the person off
I mean, it's not like anything. Oh, why are you kicking my superstar man? Superstar by the way, she called you a trafficker
She apologized today. She apologized. Tomorrow you're gonna be a trafficker for not saying nothing actually give it a couple hours
And she's gonna call you a trafficker
Because you didn't say nothing. Hey, she didn't have to say I could have got a DM. She didn't have to say that
You feel me? That was on peps. I can't I could have got a DM and said it. No, it's definitely not
Okay, man. No, that's on you
That's the one I wanted to watch though
so this
Sam remember we watched that one. Okay
Copyright crash out
Or was it
Let's see
Watched a little bit or oh is there a history? Let me see
There is
There is though
This has been this if Amber will either have a chapter
about her or someone says to me $45 and she won't be mentioned in the book
Guys, why'd you bring up the side of me? Why why you use something the fucking devil like guys
Remember that
Maybe the devil is kind of like slug words of Willy Wonka always tempting. Hey, you can do this
You can get away with this you know it that whoever's honest to Willy Wonka. It was a chocolate factory
Okay
I'm getting calls this morning saying really disgusting things really disgusting things
I can't even read what they're saying. I can't even read the disgusting messages they're sending.
It's the worst things you can say to somebody. Guys, if I was nothing, if I was nothing, if I
wasn't worth it, why would they be going after me if I wasn't like some kind of threat or something?
Like, there has to be like some reason they're obsessed with me, right? Guys, there must be
something special about me, right? It was a long time ago, maybe like six months. Yep,
And Q was like this, he was like this, he made this, he made this really stupid, he was like laughing, he was really dumb in the space of everything, he was like, I can't even, he can't even describe it, it's just like, he was like, this is like laughing, like he was like, so amused by something, oh, stupor's delight, Q said to people, yeah, he said, I got three unpaid piece of deliveries, my neighbor's on a high alert, I had to please set side of my house right now.
So anyone's gonna threaten me or my cats. Yeah, people watching the neighbors have the the things open that they're watching carefully
They're freaked out
No 2020 I can't you know I can't I
Got some good advice about that you can come into this show
Kate, you absolutely, wait, hold on, let's put Kate,
careless Kate on blast.
You can absolutely do whatever you want,
I've already cleared it,
but right now what you're doing is absolutely disgusting.
And I think you shouldn't even be here.
So you're threatening to send my,
so it's called Revenge Porn, right?
To send it to my dad.
Face down ass up. What is wrong with you? I already fucking like I don't even talk about you or care about you
But all you do is obsess over me because you couldn't get to Barry move the fuck on keeps threatening me and everything is getting documented
Yeah, my 83 year old pops is gonna have a heart attack when he sees see she's wishing death upon my dad and trying to put him
But guess what my dad is gonna outlive you because he works out every day
And he's a man that takes very good care of himself.
But Psyche, you want to have this bitch fucking threatening
this shit in your fucking channel?
No, I'm going to block her right now.
No, no, no, I already took a screenshot of it.
I'm actually putting it in the file
because this is not the first time she's harassed other females.
You fucking fuck with my family.
I always said you're going to get fucked really hard
and legal action is coming for you.
So I mean, you keep doing you.
I'll keep doing me.
I don't play dirty like you. I play with the fucking law. Okay? The fuck out of here.
Fucking bitter bitch.
Every time I go anywhere, she's on my ass
because guess what, Barry and I were friends
for a whole whopping months on the house.
Like three months, like total, if that's what he's thinking,
we were just friends.
We talked like a few times, he was there for me,
he was a friend.
And then like, he's fucking flipping out
when she's fucking over there spreading.
Everybody's seen her fat ass and her rash, yes.
Like, you know what?
Would I ever fucking threaten to send that to anybody
to give them a heart attack?
Absolutely, my dad knows. So shut the fuck up. Get a fucking light. The fuck?
This bitch is fucking like bitter, scorned, disgusting, mean, has no fucking life.
Every morning she wakes up tagging me.
She's still invested, she's still fucking jealous, she can't get over it.
It's like Vita's kitty is her new obsession.
Girl, get some fucking mental health.
You have some mental issues that need serious help and Ketamine didn't do it for you.
You need to get back on whatever prescription you need to get on because you've got fucking
mental issues.
Don't ever fucking talk about my dad.
He already knows everything.
I've already explained it to him, okay?
My dad is not opening up shit.
I'm already half shit in files.
So go ahead and keep threatening my fucking family.
I'll deal with it legally, all right?
Since we have all of your information
thanks to MJ Courts,
everything else is gonna be pretty easy to follow,
legally, okay?
I'm not a doctor like you.
I don't threaten, pussy ass bitch.
Get the fuck out of here, everyone's trolling you, the airy, everybody's trolling you, you just
didn't even know. You only saw the messages that I have, you'd be crying, you might even be a
fucking in a mental institution. Get the fuck out of here you fat hog. Jesus. Bully-ass bitch.
Yeah, let everybody document that I'm gonna send like your ass up to your dad's fucking 80 year old dad
So he can have a heart attack imagine how bitter and disgusting a human being can be that they want to give an old
Mint in a heart attack, but guess what he's protected, but just look at her character. Look how disgusting she is
Ugly inside and outside. I feel sorry for you boo. Even if you lose a 50 pounds
You always look like fucking Kathy Bays from the movie misery fucking weirdo
Go up with some brain in your braids in your hair try to look like you're a little bit of it
You still look like you put the fucking makeup on a fucking pig. They still look like a fucking pig
We all saw you bitch every day. You're talking about how I look
I see all what I mean. I mean, am I good? No, I'm fine. No, am I scared? Am I scared
Has anybody come to my house?
Except for the pizza lady. All they can do is send pizza ladies to my house
My oh, I'm getting off the line. I'm getting offline. I'm quitting YouTube
I'm quitting YouTube. There's a pizza was sent to my house three times in ten minutes
At least if you're sending a fucking pizza, why don't you pay for it? How about send me a like a real dinner?
I can just say shatter. Hey, what's up? Hello?
Dominos pizza is a hey
Is it paid for? No, no at POD paid on delivery. Well, I'm sorry. That was a prank. Okay. Thank you sir. Goodbye
Thank you Nick, I think you're pretty entertaining Nick guys guys, I'm gonna write the book
I'll give you all you guys if you want to be a part of the book, you know, I'll do a patch
I'll do it probably Kickstarter for it
I'll promote the Kickstarter and I'll get some donations.
That'll really get me writing and I'll have like little prizes like you can be mentioned
in the book, you have your name in the book, you can be in the, you can have a bright blurb
for the book, you can write opening credits, you can write a chapter, I'll have all these
different prizes if you want to like make, you want to make it up for all of us, right?
I think no, I think he was very scorn. I mean, it's like, I know Q had a crush on me
I just know it's like he was just like, you know, you can't have like that
Per like a grown man with a perm. You have many guys other than weird. I ain't gonna be
Every once in a while something big happens something that changes everything
And now in a defining moment for crypto Trump media group and crypto
Who does a perm look good on right? Not Q. I mean, it's like he's nice hair
It would be if it was like a you know a woman
It'd be very nice hair, but it's slow down gay on him. Sorry
It's like a prison hairstyle
Nice hair it was 1975 in like a nudist volleyball catalog with a big April bouncing around
Yeah, it's been like over eight months match the match the hair, right?
I don't know
Cook
Guys, why'd you bring up the side of me? Why why you summon the fucking devil like guys?
I'm actually the devil you suck like but why I was such a nice person like I was so
Kind I was so oh my god what an act I played on oh, but I know I'm actually a really kind person if you're kind to me no, but
90% of you I got that were trying to troll me. I just rolled you back by being kind right?
Guys, look at my eyes. Hold on guys. Listen to my eyes
Not the devil guys not
El Diablo
Ashton
Eblis
Bapomet
No, not
Do my eyes watch my eyes watch them
That's what I thought
I'm not the devil take it back. Hello, low key. I'm a capricorn. So I'm the devil. Yep
Yeah, yeah, whatever low key go go worship the actual devil right when you're sitting here worshiping me how about worship god?
Maybe the devil is kind of like slug worth in Willy Wonka always tempting you. Hey, you can do this
You can get away with this you know with that whoever is honest to Willy Wonka. They win the chocolate factory. You lose, okay?
I'll be the Pope whatever
Well, I'm the devil look at my eyes look at my eyes guys. Just look in my eyes
Watch them watch watch them watch them
See it you see it
Everyone go
Watch them everyone left at once. That's weird. You see it
You love me another day another breakdown. Oh John. She may water. Oh my god. Oh
Humans, oh humans, I love you so much, but I'll never understand you
I'll leave you on I'll leave you on
I install the Trojan Horse and will steal and publish your book.
Oh my gosh, how about I just like how about I write the book out in my hand and then I
go to like the Starbucks or a library and I type out the book.
How about that?
Or I have somebody else type it out for me, then I have it copyrighted.
Books I haven't written yet dumb fuck guys. No one's stealing the fucking book. I
Was stealing publish your book. Well, I'll write another book
All right another book
I have I have multiple books in me
Why you try to steal my channel
Copka-esque. Yeah, well, let's see. Let's go. Let's do copka now. Isn't that guys? Is that kind of like art interesting?
I think I think it's interesting
How about I just do whatever the fuck I want now, then I'll have to worry about being monetized. I'm still making money
You all bitches can cry about it
I'm the devil. This is old stuff
It's all this stuff. Amber, she either either if you if she if Amber will either have a chapter
About her or someone's gonna send me $45 and she won't be mentioned in the book
Barry will be in there
a whole chapter but a chapter can be one page you're calling me it's hard Kate really really Kate
Kate you look like the troll under the fucking bridge that the Billy Goats gruff
Cross over and remember the big Billy go gruff you wouldn't you wouldn't you think I'm bad meet my brother first see the book
Oh, I'll do it. I'll do it like a chap like a sample chapter
I guess so you can see that I can write and stuff like that. It'll be working
I can't read you too much about it unless until it's copyrighted though because I have all these copyright people
You can draw some great. So yeah, I want some I want some art for it. If you guys want to send some art
You guys are welcome
Guys it will be an interactive experience. It'll be like you guys can all be part of the book
Just like you I let you be part of the show you want to go off on me
You send me a hundred bucks. I'll give you a page in the book
You can say whatever shit you want about just no doxing or no threats and stuff like that
You can go off on me and say I'm a terrible person. Whatever you want to say
I'll give an example of how trolls operate and say fish taco fish taco
You want to you want to support a fish taco? Go ahead and send me 20 bucks. I'll walk down to the pier right now
Take you with me
I'll take my tarot cards there, too.
I guess there's no takers, so whatever.
So stop asking if you don't ask me to do things
if you don't plan to fund it, right?
Because now I'm not monetizing anymore.
So now I'm in a desperate situation.
How am I going to pay my rent?
How?
Ivana, you know what's fun is guys I didn't mess for like, you know
When I was 14 I did the first time then I did it when I was basically 28 to 42
I just did it for years
I've been spun you can see me spun on a few streams too, but I guys I had made it. I'll admit it
I've done it out, but I haven't done it in probably about a year. I
Hardly even smoke pot anymore
When this book ready the book will be ready for six months, but I'm gonna I'm gonna
Do a Kickstarter for it though
And oh guys, it'll be all about trolls. It'll be like the troll encyclopedia. I
Call it troll a pedia, but I don't want that to be covered. I'll call it something
The art of the troll something like I don't I'm not going too much
Guys, I'm gonna write the book. I'm gonna have other channels on this on YouTube. I'm gonna yeah
Okay, go away, fucky-lokey. Go ahead.
Olive, they're actually a great source of fiber, which feeds your friendly bacteria, except please avoid the one with the piment.
If you don't at least try this to fix your tinnitus, then honestly, you're not being smart.
I know this might sound a little crazy, but yeah, that's what it looks like.
No, it ain't the internet.
no it's fucking it's a it's fucking made in
what's it doing i didn't want to go to that
type shit bro fucking fuck is that i'm sorry that it
her like a grown man
that was it yeah i'm sorry i was like chris k is on right now
i don't know if that was his old episode or what oh i wanted to check out
tommy james thing was on but i don't know if i don't have to take out they
syndicate all the shows let me see if they did
Panel vs. VODs might have him that was on a show the other night
I don't think you I don't think it's on yet, but I think it will be
Sometimes they don't do it for a few days. Let me see. Oh the ghost overfests continue
So it must be before that hold on was that brand that same time Tommy James
Morning stream. Oh here. I think this is one is this one. I'm on this one
You want to see my appearance
That's the one that followed me on Instagram.
Fucking the hair make-up.
You want me to cut?
That's the fuck of a man in the asshole.
I'm not going to.
Hilarious.
He's calling both of us.
He actually made me laugh in the midst of all these cards.
That's sick for you, man.
That's sick for you.
Oh my god, dude, yes.
It's funny
Show a key chain
No
Yes, he does. Hey, baby Ferrari your mom
Sores likes it more than I do you fucking she likes it more than I do and I like that
I like the cringe a source likes it more than I
What the fuck you're misusing the fucking the eye because you're a faggot homosexual you're going to hell
You're going to fucking hell. You you banged me. Yeah, I don't think I've ever cried on stream
Never
Exit only faggot
I don't really get a beta tried. I mean the cringe of SARS tried to eat my ass, but I didn't let her
Sucking dick
What happens when I get the clip
When what happens when I
the world is gonna collapse in on itself that's what's gonna happen because I'm
not a fucking meth-ridden fucking turkey neck fucking tweaker who sucks dick and
like you make it you're fucking skinny because you smoke meth and you fuck
butthole get the fuck out of here nigga imagine
Imagine this greybeard telling me anything when he fucking licks butthole.
You lick poop.
You're literally retarded.
You lick where fucking waste comes out of some person's butt.
You fucking faggot.
You're like, oh I looked at where people fucking expel waste and I want to eat that and fuck
that.
You retard.
You're going to hell.
You like everything that God told you not to like.
I don't really like
You make guys grab on to the fucking skin on your neck when they fucking fail you down the throat, don't you fucking faggot
We're gonna scream it out really loud and then it will make sense. No, it's just you sound lame, bitch. Okay, shut up your mom
People should be loud and proud about the fact that f**king the faggotree is f**king hellbound.
Faggotree is hellbound.
You'll never have a baby.
You're never going to come into another man's ass and make a baby.
Your f**king microphone may be great, but you're still a faggot.
You'll f**king suck it all the way down your f**king throat because you're a better sucker than me, buddy.
Oh my god! Look at how f**king far I can shove my microphone down my throat!
You're going to hell, buddy! You're going to fucking hell, faggot!
Keep sprinkling your DNA and every guy's ass, you're going to hell.
You're going to hell.
You're going to hell, you're going to hell. Keep sucking a guy's fucking dick and drinking his gum.
You're going to hell, you're going to hell, you're going to hell.
You know why your fucking beard is turning gray because of the cum?
It's such a great line.
Oh my God, it's frosted with glue.
Really, I've done this.
I've never done this.
I'm so upset with this picture.
It's amazing.
I know you're not upset.
Why would you be upset?
If you were upset, you would suck my trucking on thread.
You don't get sarcasm, come on, come on.
I thought you were smarter than that.
You're probably a smart person, okay?
You're the one that followed me on Instagram,
you fucking weird, fucking pandering faggot.
Hey, Miss Twat, you don't have to ignore it, okay?
Just have a nice conversation.
I ignore it, okay?
I'm not the one who lets other guys fucking come in my asshole.
That works.
I don't let people come where the poo-poo comes out.
You do that.
You're going out.
You're going out!
You suck!
Look at the eye of Satan behind him.
Look, it's straight into his brown eye
while other men fucking sprinkle their seed all over it.
It's your eye, bitch, and that's why it's brown, you know?
Okay, can you like, whatever.
I'm not a fucking faggot.
I'm not going to help.
Well, you're a bitch, that's worse.
I'm allowed to fucking suck dick and take dick.
You're not.
You're boring the wrong sex,
you fucking cum drizzled faggot.
I'm beardest, drizzle and cum, I'm beardest, drizzle and cum
I justify being a faggot cause I'm a faggot
I have more viewers than you because I suck dick, because I suck dick
I take it right into my asshole and let people blow their load in my ass
Amazing dude. Wow. You're such a wonderful man. Look at this guy's fucking gray drizzle cum stained beard and his fucking rotten little turkey neck
that sucks so much jizz down it.
I will say that's always better than that.
The jizz is drying out your neck, bitch.
The jizz is drying out your neck.
It looks fucking worn out and dried out, buddy.
It's not hydrating you.
It's crispy. It's crispy.
Fuck it. Disgusting.
You suck. Yeah, you drink cold.
Don't you?
Fucking faggot.
Fuck out of here. What are you doing?
You're trying to co-op Tommy's stream?
You don't have enough fucking faggot
I'm really offended. I'm really offended, Tommy.
Oh my gosh, I'm gonna go cry about, we call the faggot.
Wow.
Because of the cocaine that you do,
and the fucking, the cum that you blow
is like a little bit powdery.
Well, it's material bitch,
if any more material is a scrimmy faggot.
It's sprinkles across somebody's asshole.
If any more material is a scrimmy faggot.
It rains down like snow a little bit.
If any more material, it's coming out.
Oh yeah, I'm sorry.
It's interesting to talk about,
but this is, it's so loud.
You too.
I'm not even on meth, and you are.
So I can do better, bitch.
You fat hog, I mean, come on.
Fat?
Oh, we lose a few pounds, okay?
I think this hurt her feelings actually. She leaves me after that.
You look like fucking Charlie Manson with Tom in your beard, nigga.
Get the fuck out of here. What the fuck are you talking about?
You're a fucking cum-bug, guzzling fucking little faggot,
headed straight to fucking Ellen. You think you're an insult matter to me, nigga?
I could take any fucking guy you would ever want. Fuckface.
I'm not gonna tell people what to do on their own show, you bitch.
I sprinkled Carmen to this guy's asshole, and now I'm maddered.
I'm maddered to IP2 because I'm a fucking crash out faggot.
And I like beacons and dick, and I love to drink cum.
And I'm a fucking faggot, and I read people's tarot cards.
And I actually pretend like I know shit when I'm actually going straight to hell.
Because I'm a fucking clumsy little faggot that drinks cum for a living.
And my bag is all right now because of the amount of cum that I drink.
Oh my God, my neck!
Why would the cow hydrate my neck?
Tell me, my feelings.
If I drink more, maybe it won't be so wrinkly like Trishalicious.
Please, predict my feelings. Tell me.
Yeah, him and vlogger and Trishalicious have the same neck.
Check that out.
Yeah, because they all fucking drag each other's fucking fluids.
That's why.
Because they all sucked each other down.
Awww.
You know what, Lisa Lampinelli copyrighted this material, okay?
You have to leave Lisa Lampinelli out of it.
In too many cities, dangerous illegals walk free.
Yeah, I might have to mute her.
I'm sorry, I know.
She's like, people that talk like that, like so loud too.
You're stealing all her jokes.
Okay, come on.
Stop.
I don't know who you're talking about.
Queen.
I don't watch all of these screeners.
I don't know what you're talking about, queen.
Maybe we should go fucking dance in the fucking gay pride parade
and wear some fucking little leather chaps.
And wear rainbow fucking bandanas and for your children.
Because we're fucking homosexuals.
We're going to hell.
Yeah.
I gotta fucking- I gotta make my fucking pride-
I know I'm to fucking people that don't use shit about it
because I like to suck cum down my throat.
Is that where I really do it?
I would say I'm doing it.
Sounds like it.
It sounds like you suck cum right down your throat
but it's not hydrating it because it's still really
wrinkly and it's coasted and dry.
You can shut up for one minute
if you had to dick in your mouth.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
Fuck.
I mean, I love dick in my mouth.
What the fuck is going on here?
So how are you gonna judge, fucking faggot?
And magic getting sprinkled, faggot?
How much DNA is on that fucking tapestry behind you?
Can you shine a UV light on it?
So we can see all the fucking rainbow come on it.
So we can see the fucking universe on your fucking tapestry, Faggot!
Shine a UV light on it, Faggot!
No!
Shine a UV light on your fucking tapestry, Faggot!
Let's see the cum!
Hey sweetheart, I don't have anything to bring.
Let's see the cum, baby!
Let's see the cum!
It could be a whole black light of your face.
And magic!
Coming on here and fucking pandering attention like a fucking faggot. What are you doing, bitch?
Fucking fucking come down your throat. How many times have I been on this fucking pan, are you?
Ask Tommy.
I'm here to talk to Tommy and stuff.
You're still here, though.
Ask Tommy a question, baby.
You're still here. You want the ginger bush right down your throat? You want Tommy's ginger
comb down your throat, baby?
Oh, I'm sorry.
out of the way, so you can suck Tommy's cup?
No, which is voluntarily, no.
Should I leave the panel, Tommy,
so this man can suck your jizz down his throat?
No, please don't, no, please don't.
Do I need to go, Psyche?
So you can suck Tommy's jizz down your throat, little daddy?
Are you mad, brother?
I'm not at all, it's just like, you know, it's kind of like that.
Then shut the fuck up!
I don't like that, though.
Don't you get enough attention, nigga!
Fuck! Imagine being like this!
Uh, I can never get enough attention.
There's never enough dicks fucking sperming all over my face!
Ugh! I gotta stream all the time!
I'm a fucking trust-fun little faggot!
I eat tear cards and drink comfort living!
Tommy can I see one question and then I'll leave and then you don't know I don't want your show to be ruined by this bitch
Okay, all I want to say is what is your um?
Yard something besides Tommy James because I don't see you on either my block list
And it's some time reason I just
Try one more time I swear
I just want to say that and it was nice meeting. Oh, yeah. Well, she's up. She left on her own
I got you. Okay
Yeah, I'm not trying to like, you know, she left on her own. I wouldn't kick her. Okay. Yeah. Hey, yo
Cringes, Laura. Thank you for going on cringes. You're always welcome and welcome to guest here. I mean, that's
I mean, it's and I love
That would probably be the last time she came on my show. I thought she was kind of funny at first
But then she was okay. I'm gonna go back at you. But anyway
I can deal with, you know, adults.
Oh yeah, that was good.
I appreciate that you didn't just leave her rage quit.
I mean, that's a big, she is over here.
I won't kick anybody.
You just leave whenever the fuck you want and let's it's sick.
Yeah, and it's like yeah, but yeah
To but then it's like I mean it's like this wasn't really I'm trying to put my show on more of like a
Tarot kind of vibe, but I still have the panel
Somebody if her you know, I don't want it down negative like I can't have that
School that you run the show like that and that's respectable and yeah
i've been able to have good conversations with you too and like at times and stuff like that and we've
gone like not gone along at times too but um yeah i have no problem with you and it's like you know
sometimes i do you know have blocked people whatever for another reason but i always
hey shit happens i don't even like i don't take any of this shit seriously or anything like that um
I'm just letting it be I want people to be able to come up here and talk and if they can't talk scream it out
But no, you're I appreciate you coming up and making that be known. All right
See, how are you doing sick? It's nice to see you and uh, not to see I'm not I don't hate sick
It's just like it was just too much for my show, but no, I don't mind you
Well, he's barely allowed here right now. So
How's rumble sick? I did promote his rumble every time didn't I let you promote your rumble?
Yeah, I did every time I was like sick tell tell your rumble and I was like, you know
I don't care you got a donation from mermaid mermaids, you know, she'd donate to whoever she wants, you know
But whatever I mean, it's like, you know, you were kind of like trying to
Probably to my face a little bit, but I don't really care like uh, what are you looking like that sick for you? Okay?
show cocaine sick
He says he has cocaine. He says he's sniffing cocaine right now. He's not talking to me
You must have cocaine because you're quiet
I don't know he might he might actually he is acting kind of like
Sick turned into Mondo
Hi chat, you know and hey Tommy James. He's a good guy and you know, everyone should support his show and your support freedom of
Speech is great that
Yeah, they support freedom of speech everywhere it exists and hey, I did like seeing you and Alex hanging out
I do like that. You know, I don't know if yeah, you don't really know but I like stayed with her for like a month
You've probably heard a little about me, but I didn't mention that nice to see you guys. She said well, she did
She um, she said that I was she said she thought she was a fast walker because she said you're like kind of a slow walker
You know, and then she's like and she's like I thought I was a fast walker, but I'm a fast walker
She said
She does walk fast, I don't care what she says. I
I was like am I walking too fast because everyone always says I walk too fast
She's like she's like you walk fast, but she's like I walk fast too
She's really like and anybody that she respects like
I, you know, I respect even like, you know, Q, which is like, I, I don't think I ever liked him like that much, but then it's like, you know,
character talking about him, give me a different perspective and like whoever, people that she actually fucks with and likes, it's like, I will fuck with, you know, in a good way, you know, because it's like.
Yeah, yeah, definitely. No, no.
Yeah. And, and actually I went to Q's the other night, I was going to help promote your show and yeah.
Oh my God. She has been so it was like right. It was like a really low time for me. Like it was just like everyone was
Yeah
She's a sweetheart
She's really the sweetheart a person and people that get on her bad side. There's a reason there's a they did something
It's like definitely she doesn't just like for no reason turn on people like people were saying oh, she'll turn on you
No, unless there's a reason she she is
very forgiving person from what I've seen, you know, and I'm a firm believer of having your own
have your own interaction and experience with somebody you can't go off like even if it's 20
people I'm stubborn I got to learn for myself even if they're right so have your own interactions
with people you guys seem to get along good that's good I definitely um like I said it's
Worked out perfectly j-buck not so much, but he's trying you know, he's trying
Like a lot of people take this shit too seriously I have my beliefs
I have my shit, but I don't fucking none of that. I don't take any of this fucking to sleep with me, man
Right. Are you are this a monetized channel Tommy or no?
Are you going to look at me?
If I can say monetize you can say monetize trust me right here. I know I probably should I'm being stupid
I really should get fucking monotone studio and then it's like right there. Just click on
Just watch the things in the monetization area
Like even say if he's probably reported my stream, but it's like I never I think YouTube likes me for some reason because
Yeah, you know never affected me, but I did
Join ice with bonuses up to $50,000 and generous benefits join dot ice dot gov
He says because you dared him if I get female ass is different it was female ass day so
My understanding my understanding of YouTube as a platform is that it's less about
What rules you break and what rules you don't break it's about the people that you have on your tail
Right, and so I and what I see people like psyche I see people like Tommy generally their strategy is to try to be friends with the trolls
To keep them on their good side, so they don't get flagged. That's why I don't stream on you to rarely do it
The only time I'm ever streaming on YouTube is if I'm doing IRL
but
Otherwise I don't stream on YouTube because it could be anything if you have the trolls if you have the
You know, yeah, I know coming from me right the neck beard basement dwellers
You can even if you have them after you and they don't like you and they want to report your channel
Doesn't even matter if you're breaking the rules or not, you know, we'll still come down
So that's why I don't stream on YouTube
I probably make more on like, you know, cash apps donations than even like on YouTube monetization and like
This is like a Lisa, like Lisa has the power chat, right? And it's like she doesn't even push members
She doesn't have memberships. She doesn't push super chat. She pushes the power chat thing and
That works fine for her and so it's like you can monetize without even being monetized on YouTube. That's not true big clips
And in the Bay Clips you're you are exactly the person that I'm describing
And I can confirm that I have not been taken down for music
It's been a number of other strikes, and I've had I think two channels
So yeah, you know, that's why I've streamed an alternative platforms because the trolls
Haven't expanded their effort on the I've never been secondary platforms
And yeah, I understand psyche what I'm saying is you don't have that problem because you know generally
me James
Tommy James and psyche strategy has been to be framed the troll
Then don't report your channel
We weren't talking to you Tommy. Well, it's his show shut up for a second. All right
Okay, yeah, I don't know. Oh, it's okay. I don't know how I like seriously
As far as the be threatening the trolls
I can't hope that the trolls are some of the more funny, relatable people to me.
And all the other accounts. I treat everybody in chat equally.
But this whole, oh, I'm friends with trolls so they don't come at me.
Sig, you've been crying about trolls since I've...
He has for years. Oh, he said this to me two years ago,
you're friends with all the trolls and all the people that make fun of me.
Just let Psyche speak. Quit talking over everybody. Have a convo.
It's fucking whack. More fake cocaine. Let's go.
It's like I start like I started like people are like, oh what you wanted to be IP to like I started like the first IRL or whatever
Like or IP to person I was on with Benny Blanco's and that's he's the first person that let me start
Promoting and you take like he let me do terror readings in his chat and stuff like that
And he promoted me to give me my first 50 subscribers and help with that
And so and then I'm like friends with saint like last night. I did a I don't know if scribbles is on IP to I don't think he is
But he I did a reading for him and his wife last night
I'm and uh
these are people that have been around for a while and they're like, you know, pretty
respect, like I just like have respect for like most, even like most trolls can be funny,
it's just the people that are like, you know, sending fucking, even the guy that sent his
fertilizer to my house, why I'm like, you know, just like, you know, I have two bags.
But usually from my experience a lot of these people won't come after you as long as you're not hurting anybody
Any animals and you're not a complete smug asshole
If you have a little redeemable quality in you, you're usually safe, but like I that's not always true either
so like
Right. I mean it's like I just
I like people, like there's like not really anybody I hate, and so it's like you know,
I just like if people are like saying like weird sexual accusations and stuff like that,
I really don't care for that, but if they're being funny, I have no problem. If there are people
that are funny, but then people just kind of turn on me too, I just kind of block them and ignore them.
If you address it, it just makes things worse.
If you don't remember if you're like,
you're trying to-
How do you go trolls?
Say, do you ban your trolls?
Do you get trolls over on Rumble?
I'm trying to understand the difference from,
that's why I stream on Rumble,
because of the trolls.
Aren't there, do you not have that many subs
or people watching you or no trolls
or what's the deal with that?
Rumble's very, I'm sorry, go ahead.
You want to, does that persig?
Like, I've been on Rumble, like first case on Rumble,
and you know, it's like the numbers
aren't going to be very big on Rumble.
It's just such a small platform,
but it's good that people are trying to like,
you get it going and stuff.
I'm syndicated on it by Panelverse,
and I think you are too, by the same person, Tom.
I think so.
Are you on Panelverse VOD?
I think you might be.
Yeah, yeah, I'm on that, yeah.
And that's cool, so it's like any.
Let me show my delete it will be on rumble and stuff like that so it's a kind of like keeps an archive for me without having to like
Don't I think it's important somebody did that
Here's the thing I chat I might keep on
Just as long as he's being subdued, I never knew Coke to make someone like quiet and withdrawn like that
But he might have ADHD
But I said you don't have to answer my questions
Even though you want to talk questions and talk over everybody it might be important, right?
This is why mommy's I'll still keep you on for a little bit, but I'm trying to teach you and help you
I want you to have a conversation
I asked you a question and you to play the silent treatment game
And still want to hang out up here, I should boot him off right now, but I will get better this way. So we'll keep him
This is a few days ago like three days ago, probably it's like he hits a wall every now and then and his feelings get hurt
And this is what he does. So, you know what I have to do
W I'm laughing and smiling and sing is
Sad and hurt and we're gonna keep along because it's funny. This is why
This is a defeated SIG. This is SIG when he's all out of ammo
And he's like been dealt with by cringe dealt with by Tommy. He don't want no smoke no more
I get it. W and I don't have to cope. I don't have to cope to throw it up
But anyway, that's stupid that's neither here or there all right, but no, I mean, uh
You know IP2 is way dead dead way dead
Don't get me wrong. Do I wish there was a comeback and there'd be people do an IRL and like making it fucking degenerate and fun again?
Sure, but I don't see that happening. I decided to like
You know because I liked what I liked about IP to is that hey, there's a website that shows when live streamer
Oh, yeah, that's cool. I didn't know about the like well
They're trying to like make the streamers all low cows and like, you know when I commit SCYC IDE and so
That's why I started my own thing
Called psyche verse org and you can like it's almost up and I'm gonna be putting like, you know
friend of mine and the people that are like in the community and stuff up there.
It's going to be do the same exact thing shows when people are alive and things
like that. And so, you know, and it's like, I'm happy to like help.
And it's like, how did anybody promote to it? Like, you know, most people, I make
mods, you know, as long as they're like, you know, respectful and stuff in the
chat, because I need mods to be respectful. I can't like, I had Alexander
McQueen as a mod and then it's like,
Yeah, it was really and then he was calling people this lady a bitch her name was Guadalupe Guacamole
He's like oh this bitch is stalking me
I'm like well you can't call people bitches you're a mod and I unmodded him
Unhit her and then she turns out to be the sweetest person and they donated and they got a terrarium stuff
It was so sweet and so and then I have to be a little bit like more
How the liver warns us it's overworked.
This nutrient will change your body.
I'm strict because, you know, I am monetized and things like that.
And I would like to, you know, just, you know, be monetized for the community and stuff.
And I want to help people and make this my career and things like that.
Well, I hate to do this, but I want to give everybody a final word.
I'm going to recap something and then end the stream.
Any final words?
I just want to thank you Tommy for having me on okay. You have a great rest of the show. Thank you SIG and you know
Could just source. I'm sorry if I was too hard on you and no hard feelings. Have a good night everybody. Thank you for having me on
Bye
That wasn't too bad I
Try to be friendly. Oh, I do. I'm doing pretty good. Yeah
Yeah, I know
Like last night I was on like someone's show because I was asked kind of asked to come up and then like
You know, there's there's two people there that may not like me
But everyone's pretty respectful
I got fucking blogger on it and blogger was actually like, you know
Well, he tried to come at me a little bit and he wanted to I think just for for like fun because he wasn't like
Wasn't that bad with like anything he said, but then he came at me and then I like came right back at him
It's like with like better
arguments. Plus, I teased him a little bit earlier. I was like, yeah, there's a
story about the blogger butthole with that picture with like, there's a
picture of like some strange looking something. I don't know what I was
looking in that picture, but it was odd.
Well, yeah, and I do like try to like look at people's like, you know
She might have had like someone that yelled at her like that or something like that
I have no idea but it's like there's or it's just like but it's like, you know, you know
There's like some kind of sensitive person in there somewhere. That's like putting on a show, right?
And it's like and then it's like that's what I don't want to like hurt like what I could so I
Felt kind of like bad and she like quit. I didn't know if I had something to do with it, but
Because I don't want to like trigger people like that bad
But there are a lot of things that are like you wouldn't know that they're triggers for people and so it's and it's like
Especially when you're psychic you might like pick up on some of these things and then you say that and it's like it's not good
You know, I don't know and so I've it's kind of harder to communicate sometimes
So I've make sense, I don't know I'm sure like a lot of women understand like psychics and like
My gosh, and I need to fix this. Oh, that works. Okay. I was looking the second verse is like, oh, I was working on it all night and it's like it's like
And there's a few things that I'm getting annoyed with this stuff out software like it's like it takes a long time sometimes even though
It does like help you a lot. It's like
Still very I wouldn't oh just figuring out programming alone. What a nightmare. I could never be that patient. I would
But I am taking a coding course on some website. I'm on but
Just so I could like understand code a little better, but it's so complicated. Oh for me, you know
It started at the very beginning which sort of that's the easy stuff and it's pretty good if it's the basic stuff
Wow
Okay
Yeah, I still have a little bit to do with my I started to get it
Good. Oh shit
Yeah, so today we're celebrating my aunts. I don't know if it's her birthday. It would have been her birthday or something
But she passed away this year
Oh, yeah, she passed away this year and she was always like the controversial ants, you know, she was my she was aunt
I won't say her name, but
she
She was always looking kind of like the black sheep, you know, she was you know, my
grandparents like
Or my my uncle was a cop right so my grandparents that raised her they raised a cop and then my mom and then
And then she and like they're all good-looking people
But she was like, you know, she kind of fell in with the rough crowd or whatever
So we first we knew of her as a gay alcoholic and then we heard about her
She had a friend quote unquote named Carmen and stuff. She moved to Texas by the way. She moved to Texas and
So she was always come from Texas with her, you know trailer or car
She had these this dog the ugliest dog I've ever seen in my life. It's like it's like little hairless dog
She had a few of those
She always promised you take me to the pier and go fishing for tuna, but we never ever did she never did
She was really sweet like she tried to send this like little like dollar to on Christmas and our birthdays and it's like
No, I was just probably all you know her best
And I know she like bought her dentist like she did she would dig she learned how she washed all the windows of the dentist building
It started this washing window washing business
So she could like pay for her teeth and other things and then she would bring her girlfriend's home and her girlfriend was like the six foot tall
woman like I think her name was like I want to say her name but she was just she was very tall
and like she was like a king of the hill character like a real life king of the hill character
she's like oh she kind of like was like Hank Hill or Bill or something like that but she's like
this blonde lady with you know she looks like you know big blonde and uh
Yeah, and so and then and then she then my aunt quit drinking found Jesus and like which it was like very like
You know very like hot and then you know all about Jesus and stuff
But she was always very friendly loved the family and then she died very suddenly about some kind of
Brain cancer or something my uncle died of some kind of horrible of cancer brain cancer. I think and like
So I don't know. It's just like my parents have lost all their brothers and sisters
There's the last one's left and you know, I think about my brothers and sisters are seven kids
And so it's like I have six people like that. I mean, you know, I'd hate to have to watch anybody, you know go and
But yeah, I have big Brady Bunch family so
Yeah, let me see. Yeah, I got to
Oh, I'm kind of out of tobacco, but I already walked to McDonald's and maybe I'll walk back and get a coffee later
But they're not not until they open at nine o'clock. I mean, it was probably scrape a little stuff off my table right now and
Our tobacco I'm trying to get my meals dirty because look how clean they clean nice. They are it's been a long time in the
the bath good to sure they're got all clean but I
Don't have touching something and like right now
Here comes the backer
The weed too wow the weed like really like knocked me out that first day. He's Samantha
Did anybody see that
Well, I think oh, yeah, I think I might want to play like a song let me see now I can play kind of music
I won't tell you.
Oh my gosh, that works.
Yeah, some of the pages on my site keepers
are going to rumble and stuff.
I have no idea why.
Let me see if I can find some weird stuff along.
Okay, let me see if I can download this stuff.
Okay.
I wanna find stuff not.
Yeah, I was way too high last time when I was trying to figure out how to show something.
I can do it!
Do you see it?
Ah, look at that!
Pretty cool
Then I start freezing
Restarted, okay. I don't know some people don't like that. So, oh, yeah people are leaving. Well, oh well
Can't help it I didn't make these by the way, I found these on Instagram
But just realize I'm not gonna play anything that that harsh
Promise I share my share screen
It's all
Almost no, it's not I don't know why it's not working really bad quality
Sister when I try to show people stuff sometimes
But now it's not going back to the...
Understand this.
Well...
Should...
We should be able to skip...
Yeah.
Should we start it?
Let's see.
One more time.
to claim it's how i got this far more i can't believe it that i got this call so i succeeded
passenger walk more look like river famous first happy birthday
She's the best of them all.
Thank you for watching, please subscribe and hit that like button!
That was about to turn into that
I am by the sea where the grass is green and the sound's safe deep
uh, fuck it sounds like
They're gonna not sell swishers sweets anymore like liquor store told me oh, they're not very discontinuing selling them because they have the names
California won't allow us to sell them anymore in anywhere in the state because they have the word sweet and on it even there
Sweet
Yeah, I don't know, I remember they go to the song, I don't know, I haven't played that song ever again, so he thought that it was me.
He might be that person who knows.
You don't want to go play my VR game.
I saw Madagos.
It usually happened last night, Samantha.
That was crazy.
Absolutely insane.
But then he hasn't written me back since, really.
You can play the Gaudi song.
I like the Gaudi song.
Out of New York, came a storm on wheels, rolling in smooth with the mafia feels, Cuban cigar, lit like it's temper, pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner, said psyche, I'm bored, had to switch the scene, left some poor woman screaming on live stream, trolled her down to the void and back, then crashed my show like a heart attack, got it, made, made!
But we friends, forever my friend
He thinks he's God
With the lowercase G in a wheelchair
Still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf
Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief
Brought spunky two now that trolls a gem
Cameras glitchin', chat on fire
Mods beggin' me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test, stop the mess
We friends, forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat, then held it down
You got layers, like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade, a heart made of ice
And maybe rice, so let's light that cigar
Raise the mic, another night of chaos
the drama the heat the fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one got it yeah
you crazy but your family now rolling through fire still taking a bow no matter
the madness no matter the weather but we stick together
You were in that spunky. I know there's a spunky song. I don't remember.
Okay, you want to, you want to...
They dox, they slander.
Yeah, okay, I'm gonna wrap it up. Oh, you want a link? Okay, help me out. Come on. I won't wrap it up
Okay, you have a good day, Spunky
But at the ball pistol
Thank you enjoy your Sunday, too
Hello, good morning. Good morning. How are you? Oh hungover. It's shit. Oh
If unless I
I don't remember
You don't remember. Oh, no
You didn't make up for the sore booty hole, did you?
I don't know. I think she took advantage of me. Oh, no
Well, you know, did you take advantage of me?
I was like, I don't know. I don't remember it. He's like, did you wake up with a store booty hole?
I'm like, I think she might think that Dan could jump me.
She did
Yeah, I think
She's stuck things inside of me. Oh my gosh. Well, that can be fun as long as they're not
Breakable, you know, you just have seen some of those
shows you've never been on one of those episodes have you
Imagine you maybe being experimental, you know, there's dumb things on there
But yeah, the worst thing is like a list of
Things that people have, you know surgeons have taken out of people, you know, like lacy
Hi come say hi
I live in the energy last night. I was on that thing. Yeah, dude. This this time change is killing me
The time change. Hi. How are you? Yeah? I'm not used to this West Coast time, you know
I hear it's actual color or is that I was seeing it was a week because I hate that color. It's like
You've never seen it like I even here died that color like really successfully
I have yeah
Yeah, we take advantage of me last night. Sure. Is that why my vocal hurts? Yeah
There's a rosemary's baby. It's like that's
She she like it's he has been drugs her with like chocolate pudding
And then she got a we got to get ready for my sister's wedding. We got to go return the car out there
You're for your sister's wedding. Yes
The area in Long Beach and that and I got friend of yours from there or like oh, yeah, she's your ex-girlfriend
She said we have a stranger. I don't even know this one. I live in Long Beach. I don't even know you want to hang out
Yes, okay after I leave PV. I'm from PV and like we're going to be to the South Bay area
so but
Yeah, let me just down the road
cool guy
Have you a fun day at the wedding? Are you dressing all up and like you know, we look like a yes
I bought her a very nice expensive dress
It's fucking gorgeous
And I have a tuxedo
You trust him you trusted him with your dress. That's kind of brave, but no she picked out the dress
I just like my card. Okay. Nice
That's awesome
Anything else?
You just have a wonderful day like
He he over served me last night you did what'd you drink? That's one of the fireball. I ran out of fireball
And I started drinking Jack Daniels. Okay. Yeah, that'll do that hard alcohol. Watch out for the
Drunk again today. Well, is there open bar? Yes, there is
The best part about weddings, huh?
That's the best part about weddings.
Honestly, the best part is getting drunk in front
of my family, because they hate alcohol.
Are you giving a speech?
What?
They hate alcohol?
Yeah, my family is going to be counting my drinks.
OK.
They just gave me.
All right.
Have a good day, LD.
See you later.
You too, man.
I'll see you later.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
That a Putin tattoo on her arm. I don't know that what I think it's like it was like some bald guy
I don't know it would be I would be on a few putin I tattoo on your arm wouldn't it
Already just for Halloween is to have to know well
This is just like a little a little day jacket. You know like a little like mr. Rogers, huh?
It's like with a little at this
This is a nice little little windbreaker. I have and then I have this nice little shirt and I have this thing for aunt my aunt today
You know, she she passed away like she was pretty relative. She's my mom's younger sister
So, you know, it's always like, you know, can you imagine like but I have it's like I said
I have six other siblings and plus all their spouses imagine all those funerals like that happened over the years
I mean, it's like and like one person is gonna go to all of them and then one person nobody's gonna go to
You ever think that about that about funerals with families and stuff like that. That's kind of creepy thought, right?
I'm sorry
Um, it looks like but it looks like yeah, I'll wrap up now. So have a good day guys
Um, I'll be back maybe before
But maybe not the time is it it's eight. So yeah, okay. Okay. Love you guys
Talk to you soon
Alex walks the beat in the
I've been missing in my sleep
She's gutting the trout, he's eatin' steaks
Somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his nightsticks for a fishin' pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol, old page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say